What could be the cause of this massive
mosquito outbreak this year?
We ask Mr. Kafetch,
a mosquito expert who has written
several books on the subject.
Thank you for having me.
Well, let me come right to the point.
These mosquitos belong
to an entirely new species.
Therefore, I know nothing about them.
Get out of here!
Ahem, excuse me.
Now, let's take a look at the areas
- likely to be hit hardest by the outbreak.
- Man, City Z's in their path.
Now we've got a mosquito outbreak?
We interrupt this program
for breaking news.
A large swarm of mosquitos
has been sighted in City Z.
Mummified remains of attacked
farm animals have also been found.
If you encounter a swarm of mosquitos,
flee immediately.
This is an emergency evacuation warning.
Threat level: Demon.
No resident is to go outside
under any circumstances.
I repeat...
No City Z resident
is to go outside...
Acquiring target.
The
LONE CYBORG
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
nan datten da, frustration
Are you talking to him? Frustration ☹
ore wa tomaranai
He's not going to stop
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
power, get power
Power, get power
girigiri genkai made
On to the very edge
Hero
ore o tataeru koe ya
There are voices praising him
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
but he's not doing this for acclaim
Hero
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
So he just fight evil without end
Nobody knows who he is
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
Hero
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
tatakau hero
A fighting hero
kodoku na hero
A lone hero
I
i wanna be a saikyou hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
Thanks to that warning,
they're all empty!
Like someone's gonna die
from a mosquito bite.
What's losing
a little blood if I get all this?
The wind...?
What the--?!
Come on, you guys.
That wasn't nearly enough.
Go get some more for me!
Target acquired.
I see.
You make them suck the blood,
then take it all for yourself.
You must be controlling the mosquitos
via some sort of signal.
That would explain
their mysterious behavior.
So if I were to get rid of you,
the leader,
would the swarm disperse too?
Our next meal is here.
Go drain him dry.
Incinerate.
I'll eliminate you.
So try no to move.
You're going to eliminate me?
Come on and try it!
Did I get it?
Damn...mosquitos!!
Incinerate.
Maybe a leg next?
Wait, where are my legs?
Futile effort.
I won't let you escape.
What the hell is that guy?
He's gonna get me
if I don't do something now.
The townspeople may
all be hiding...
but there are plenty
of animals around.
Come here, little ones.
Empty all your stored juices into me!
So many.
If she's been collecting blood
from the whole town and beyond,
then it may not simply be
a food source for her.
I should put an end to this
as soon as possible.
Get back here, dammit!
You and I aren't done yet!
What's with this guy?
It's in my mouth!
Pft! Pft! You little--!
Huh?
What's that squirming over there?
Huh? Mosquitoes?!
You over there.
Evacuate now.
That swarm is conscious.
If it senses you,
it will immediately attack.
Seriously?
That's bad. I gotta get--
Since you spoke, I thought you would have
at least human-level intelligence.
But, In the end, you were just a bug.
You brought all the mosquitos together
into one, easy-to-burn swarm.
When I spotted you,
I confirmed there were
no living beings within 500 meters,
so I should have been free to fire away.
Wait, that guy might have--
Man, you saved me.
You're amazing.
What was that just now?
You totally made them bug out!
Ba-dum-dum-tsh.
Oh, I was just trying to make a joke
about the mosquitos being bugs, and...
Idiots!
I no longer need the tiny ones.
Because...
...look...
how strong I've become!!
Can't your punches
kill a little mosquito?
Weakling!
Now I see.
The more blood she consumes,
the more powerful she becomes.
I think I'll have your head next!
I let my guard down.
There's no chance of winning.
All I can do is self-destruct.
Forgive me, Doctor...
Mosquitos...suck!
Hold on!
Please tell me your name!
Oh. It's Saitama.
I'd like to be your disciple.
Oh, okay.
Huh?
Editor & Timer :
ScavvyKiD
[AnimeRG]
Sub General: IsoTropic
Sub Soldier: KoTuWa
Editor & Timer :
ScavvyKiD
[AnimeRG]
Sub General: IsoTropic
Sub Soldier: KoTuWa
Editor & Timer :
ScavvyKiD
[AnimeRG]
Sub General: IsoTropic
Sub Soldier: KoTuWa
Editor & Timer :
ScavvyKiD
[AnimeRG]
Sub General: IsoTropic
Sub Soldier: KoTuWa
Sensei!
You really showed up.
Uh...
It's "Genos," Saitama-sensei.
Can you not call me sensei?
Master!
Not Master either!
Go back to your home after your drink.
I'm not looking for disciples.
Wait--you're back in one piece?
Yes, my body is mostly mechanical.
As long as there are parts,
repairs are quick.
You're an odd one.
What kind of parts
do you use, Master?
Don't use any.
Then what about the
skin-colored armor on your head?
Yeah, that's my skin.
But that would mean you're bald
despite being so young.
So I'm bald--what's your problem?!
Me? You'll listen to my problems?
No thanks, I'm good.
Actually, four years ago, when I was 15,
I was still a real human being.
Did you hear what I just said?
Although we had to pinch pennies,
my family and I lived
a peaceful and fairly happy life.
But one day, a crazy cyborg went out of
control and attacked our town.
The insane cyborg...
Most likely, a failed body modification
generated an irregularity in his brain.
He destroyed everything in sight.
Parks, schools, buildings, my house...
He even took my family's lives.
Miraculously I survived,
but being only a weak 15-year-old,
I was alone and at the end of my strength
in a ruined town.
That's when Doctor Kuseno happened
to pass through.
Doctor Kuseno, a scientist for justice,
was on a mission to stop the destruction
caused by the rampaging cyborg.
That's when I asked Doctor Kuseno to
perform body modification surgery on me.
That's how I was reborn as a cyborg
who fights for justice.
I promised Doctor Kuseno that one day
I would terminate the evil cyborg.
I see--
It's been four years since that day.
I'm now 19 and I've been wandering
from town to town eliminating evil.
The number of monsters and criminal
organizations I have destroyed
are too many to count.
But I have been unable to find any clues
about that insane cyborg
and have become increasingly
frustrated and restless.
I find myself chasing a virtual image
of that cyborg
whenever I square off against
my enemies.
Then last week, when that mosquito
monster appeared,
I let my concentration slip.
I was convinced I could not lose to anything
but the rampaging cyborg,
so I neglected to even analyze the data
on my opponent and rushed to confront her.
The result, as you know,
was that an opponent
with immense strength bested me.
If you, Master Saitama,
had not been in the area,
I would have undoubtedly
been destroyed.
Master, you saved my life.
My life that was once saved by
Doctor Kuseno
has now been saved again by you,
Master Saitama.
I feel the weight of that responsibility.
I must not die before
destroying that cyborg.
And to do that, I must continue
fighting evil as a righteous cyborg
until he appears before me one day.
I need to get stronger.
Last week,
when I saw your punch,
I knew I had to study under you
as your disciple.
If only I could be
as strong as you, Master Saitama!
I have an old enemy to defeat,
and the battle is not for me only.
It's for my hometown,
and for Doctor Kuseno too.
I realize I am still inexperienced.
But right now,
I need enormous power
so I can eradicate
the greatest of evils!
Doctor Kuseno is--
Enough, you idiot!
Shorten it to 20 words or less!
Mosquito Girl was defeated?
With one punch, you say?
Well, she was merely
a prototype, after all.
Why is he naked?
Unknown.
Well, whatever.
He'll make an excellent specimen.
We shall study his physiology--
by force if necessary.
Send a messenger
and invite him here,
to our "House of Evolution."
Master, here's the short version:
Please teach me the way
to become strong like you.
- Genos...
- Yes!
How old are you?
19.
So young...
I'm sure you'll surpass me in no time.
Do you mean that?
I'm 25 now, but I was 22
when I started training in the summer.
Sure, I'll teach you.
But, remember, it won't be easy.{But it won't be easy.
Can you handle it?}
Yes, sir!!
Object approaching at high speed--
It's here!
Huh?
My name is...huh?
Pay for my ceiling!
So...
Hm?
It seems our advance agent,
Kamakyuri, is down.
I can't sense him
with my telepathy anymore.
What? Wasn't he one of
our stronger guys?
There are two more outside.
Master, leave them to me!
Don't bust people's ceilings!
Oh, never mind.
Can't you guys just
come through the door?
M-Master!
Don't worry, I'm good.
I kinda feel like a...bamboo shoot.
Elevated energy levels detected.
A cyborg?
Could it be...?
You are not the target.
What's going on? I can't see.
You are in the way!
I have some questions for you.
It would appear you're in
what they call a "tight spot."
Well done, Ground Dragon!
GROUND DRAGON
It complicates things
if they put up a fight.
Master!
You dare to look away?
Quite courageous!
I am the pinnacle of
the House of Evolution's science.
I am Armored Gorilla.
Your attacks have no effect on me.
The "House of Evolution"?
What does it want with my master?
It is none of your business.
And it is our rule that anyone who
oppose us, will be eliminated without fail.
I must destroy you.
Hey, bastard!
What's with that look?
Being underground keeps you cool,
but at the same time,
it's nice and warm.
I'm feeling sleepy. So, could you go away?
It seems like I need to show you your place.{I see I need to
teach you your place.}
Listen up! I'm gonna slice
your eyes out with these!
Then we'll see if you resist!
The Beast King never
lets anyone off easy.
Well, enough fooling around.
If you wanna apologize,
now's your chance.
You guys smashed my ceiling!
Humph. Fine.
Then behold the true power
- Aw man...
- of the Beast--
I got dirt in my belt.
Hey, are you listening?
Let me just shake this out.
You done?
One sec.
I'm done.
Okay, then behold the true
power of the Beast King!
Lion Slash!
You okay, Frog Man--
Outta the way, pissants!
Such is the law of the jungle!
And you're next!
Wait! Don't kill him yet!
Lion Slash: Meteor Power Shower!!
Consecutive...
Normal Punches.
Oh.
N-No one told me
he'd be like that!
It's best we retreat now and regroup...
Found you!
No waayyy!
Huh?
Answer the question or be eliminated.
Your choice.
It is you who will be eliminated.
You fool.
I am the third most powerful
fighter in the "House of Evolution."
At your power level,
you will never beat the Beast King,
the second most powerful.
You will be destroyed.
You're talking about this guy?
Apparently so.
Look, I'm really sorry.
I'll tell you everything,
just don't kill me!
What the hell?
What happened to your robotic voice?
Sorry, I was just trying
to sound cool.
Hey, come back home soon
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
I close my eyes and think of you
I want to see you... I feel like crying
I feel so romantic
I hope these feelings reach you
I know very well
how hard you work all the time
You're the one I love
You're so strong but I'm still worried
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
I'll find you before any stars
Come straight back home
Hey, come back home soon
What do you mean?
The hit team wiped out?
- How did this happen?
- Wait, don't jump to conclusions yet.
- It may be a mistake.
- Verify the report immediately!
- Right away.
- Be careful!
What's all this commotion about?
NEXT
EPISODE
THE OBSESSIVE SCIENTIST
Okay, time for Mosquito Girl's episode preview!
Next week's story will be about my birthplace.
I was born--what?!
Time's up already?!
Oh, all right.
The next episode of One Punch Man
is episode 3, "The Obsessive Scientist."
Scientist, huh? Who could that be?